Finding Aid for the University of Tennessee Theatre Collection, 1901- AR.0235
University of Tennessee Libraries, Special Collections
- Plays, 1941 February 18-2010 December 2-19; I; (Playbills, Photographs, Press Clippings, Production Materials, Posters, Stage Designs, and Scrapbooks)
  - Individual Plays, 1941 February 18-2010 December 19; A; (Playbills, Photographs, Press Clippings, Production Materials, Posters, Stage Designs, and Scrapbooks)
    - The Tax Collector (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1977 January 28-February 12; (1 of 4); (Programs and Press Clippings) (Box 7, Folder 73)
    - The Tax Collector (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1977 January 28-February 12; (2 of 4); (Photographs) (Box 7, Folder 74)
    - The Tax Collector (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1977 January 28-February 12; (3 of 4); (Negatives) (Box 7, Folder 75)
    - The Tax Collector (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1977 January 28-February 12; (4 of 4); (Financial Materials) (Box 7, Folder 76)
    - Cat On a Hot Tin Roof (Carousel Theatre), 1977 February 11-19; (Playbills) (Box 7, Folder 77)
    - Ghosts, 1977 March 25-April 9; (1 of 2); (Playbills) (Box 7, Folder 78)
    - Ghosts, 1977 March 25-April 9; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 7, Folder 79)
    - The Brothers (Carousel Theatre), 1977 May; (1 of 2); (Playbill) (Box 7, Folder 80)
    - The Brothers (Carousel Theatre), 1977 May; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 7, Folder 81)
    - Ruddygore (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1977 May; (1 of 2); (Playbills) (Box 7, Folder 82)
    - Ruddygore (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1977 May; (2 of 2); (Negatives/Contact Sheets) (Box 7, Folder 83)
    - Tavern (Clarence Brown Theatre), circa 1977 June; (Negatives) (Box 7, Folder 84)
    - Do You Turn Somersaults? (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1977 August 4-5, 8-13; (1 of 4); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 7, Folder 85)
    - Do You Turn Somersaults? (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1977 August 4-5, 8-13; (2 of 4); (Photographs) (Box 7, Folder 86)
    - Do You Turn Somersaults? (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1977 August 4-5, 8-13; (3 of 4); (Negatives) (Box 7, Folder 87)
    - Do You Turn Somersaults? (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1977 August 4-5, 8-13; (4 of 4); (Production Materials) (Box 7, Folder 88)
    - I Missed the Bus (Theatre 2), 1977 August 18-20; (1 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 7, Folder 89)
    - I Missed the Bus (Theatre 2), 1977 August 18-20; (2 of 2); (Production Materials) (Box 7, Folder 90)
    - Medicine Show (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1977 September 30-October 15; (1 of 3); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 7, Folder 91)
    - Medicine Show (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1977 September 30-October 15; (2 of 3); (Photographs) (Box 7, Folder 92)
    - Medicine Show (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1977 September 30-October 15; (3 of 3); (Production Materials) (Box 7, Folder 93)
    - Equus (Carousel Theatre), 1977 November 4-12; (1 of 3); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 7, Folder 94)
    - Equus (Carousel Theatre), 1977 November 4-12; (2 of 3); (Photographs) (Box 7, Folder 95)
    - Equus (Carousel Theatre), 1977 November 4-12; (3 of 3); (Production Materials) (Box 7, Folder 96)
    - Peter Pan (Carousel Children's Theatre), 1977 November 21-23, December 1-2; (1 of 2); (Press Clippings) (Box 7, Folder 97)
    - Peter Pan (Carousel Children's Theatre), 1977 November 21-23, December 1-2; (2 of 2); (Production Materials) (Box 7, Folder 98)
    - Hamlet (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1977 November 18-December 10; (1 of 5); (Playbills, Flyers, and Press Clippings) (Box 7, Folder 99)
    - Hamlet (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1977 November 18-December 10; (2 of 5); (Photographs) (Box 7, Folder 100)
    - Hamlet (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1977 November 18-December 10; (3 of 5); (Negatives) (Box 7, Folder 101)
    - Hamlet (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1977 November 18-December 10; (4 of 5); (Production Materials) (Box 7, Folder 102)
    - Hamlet (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1977 November 18-December 10; (5 of 5); (Box Office/Financial Materials) (Box 7, Folder 103)
    - The Imaginary Invalid (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1978 January 6-21; (1 of 4); (Playbills, Flyers, and Press Clippings) (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - The Imaginary Invalid (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1978 January 6-21; (2 of 4); (Photographs) (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - The Imaginary Invalid (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1978 January 6-21; (3 of 4); (Negatives) (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - The Imaginary Invalid (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1978 January 6-21; (4 of 4); (Production Materials) (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - A Midsummer Night's Dream (Carousel Theatre), 1978 February 3-25; (1 of 4); (Playbills, Flyers, and Press Clippings) (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - A Midsummer Night's Dream (Carousel Theatre), 1978 February 3-25; (2 of 4); (Photographs) (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - A Midsummer Night's Dream (Carousel Theatre), 1978 February 3-25; (3 of 4); (Negatives) (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - A Midsummer Night's Dream (Carousel Theatre), 1978 February 3-25; (4 of 4); (Production Materials) (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - It's About Time (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1978 February 24-March 4; (1 of 2); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - It's About Time (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1978 February 24-March 4; (2 of 2); (Production Materials) (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - The Beaux' Stratagem (Carousel Theatre), 1978 April 7-15; (1 of 3); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - The Beaux' Stratagem (Carousel Theatre), 1978 April 7-15; (2 of 3); (Photographs) (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - The Beaux' Stratagem (Carousel Theatre), 1978 April 7-15; (3 of 3); (Production Materials) (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Harvey (Carousel Theatre), 1978 May 19-27; (1 of 3); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Harvey (Carousel Theatre), 1978 May 19-27; (2 of 3); (Photographs) (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Harvey (Carousel Theatre), 1978 May 19-27; (3 of 3); (Production Materials) (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Flemming (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1978 September 22-October 14; (1 of 4); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Flemming (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1978 September 22-October 14; (2 of 4); (Photographs) (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Flemming (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1978 September 22-October 14; (3 of 4); (Negatives) (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Flemming (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1978 September 22-October 14; (4 of 4); (Production Materials) (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Taming of the Shrew (Carousel Theatre), 1978 November 3-18; (1 of 4); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Taming of the Shrew (Carousel Theatre), 1978 November 3-18; (2 of 4); (Photographs) (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Taming of the Shrew (Carousel Theatre), 1978 November 3-18; (3 of 4); (Negatives) (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Taming of the Shrew (Carousel Theatre), 1978 November 3-18; (4 of 4); (Production Materials) (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - A Funny Thing Happened On the Way to the Forum (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1978 November 17-December 2; (1 of 4); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - A Funny Thing Happened On the Way to the Forum (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1978 November 17-December 2; (2 of 4); (Photographs) (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - A Funny Thing Happened On the Way to the Forum (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1978 November 17-December 2; (3 of 4); (Negatives) (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - A Funny Thing Happened On the Way to the Forum (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1978 November 17-December 2; (4 of 4); (Production Materials) (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Alice in Wonderland (Carousel Children's Theatre), circa 1978 November 29-December 6; (Production Materials) (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - The Hot L Baltimore (Carousel Theatre), 1979 February 16-March 3; (1 of 4); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - The Hot L Baltimore (Carousel Theatre), 1979 February 16-March 3; (2 of 4); (Photographs) (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - The Hot L Baltimore (Carousel Theatre), 1979 February 16-March 3; (3 of 4); (Negatives) (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - The Hot L Baltimore (Carousel Theatre), 1979 February 16-March 3; (4 of 4); (Production Materials) (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - A Meeting by the River (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1979 February 24-March 10; (1 of 4); (Playbills, Flyers, and Press Clippings) (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - A Meeting by the River (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1979 February 24-March 10; (2 of 4); (Photographs) (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - A Meeting by the River (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1979 February 24-March 10; (3 of 4); (Negatives) (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - A Meeting by the River (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1979 February 24-March 10; (4 of 4); (Production Materials) (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - As You Like It (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1979 March 30-April 21; (1 of 5); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - As You Like It (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1979 March 30-April 21; (2 of 5); (Photographs) (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - As You Like It (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1979 March 30-April 21; (3 of 5); (Negatives) (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - As You Like It (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1979 March 30-April 21; (4 of 5); (Production Materials) (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - As You Like It (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1979 March 30-April 21; (5 of 5); (Box Office/Financial Materials) (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - A Streetcar Named Desire (Carousel Theatre), 1979 April 20-May 5; (1 of 2); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - A Streetcar Named Desire (Carousel Theatre), 1979 April 20-May 5; (2 of 2); (Negatives) (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - Born Yesterday (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1979 May 18-June 2; (1 of 4); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - Born Yesterday (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1979 May 18-June 2; (2 of 4); (Photographs) (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - Born Yesterday (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1979 May 18-June 2; (3 of 4); (Negatives) (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - Born Yesterday (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1979 May 18-June 2; (4 of 4); (Production Materials) (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - Many Moons (Carousel Children's Theatre), 1979 May 29-June 1; (Production Materials) (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - A Horse of a Different Color (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1979 June 29-July 21; (1 of 3); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - A Horse of a Different Color (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1979 June 29-July 21; (2 of 3); (Photographs) (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - A Horse of a Different Color (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1979 June 29-July 21; (3 of 3); (Production Materials) (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - Oh! What a Lovely War (Carousel Theatre), 1979 October 5-20; (1 of 4); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - Oh! What a Lovely War (Carousel Theatre), 1979 October 5-20; (2 of 4); (Photographs) (Box 8, Folder 54)
    - Oh! What a Lovely War (Carousel Theatre), 1979 October 5-20; (3 of 4); (Negatives) (Box 8, Folder 55)
    - Oh! What a Lovely War (Carousel Theatre), 1979 October 5-20; (4 of 4); (Production Materials) (Box 8, Folder 56)
    - Twelfth Night (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1979 November 9-24; (1 of 5); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 8, Folder 57)
    - Twelfth Night (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1979 November 9-24; (2 of 5); (Photographs) (Box 8, Folder 58)
    - Twelfth Night (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1979 November 9-24; (3 of 5); (Photographs (Box 8, Folder 59)
    - Twelfth Night (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1979 November 9-24; (4 of 5); (Negatives) (Box 8, Folder 60)
    - Twelfth Night (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1979 November 9-24; (5 of 5); (Production Materials) (Box 8, Folder 61)
    - A Christmas Carol (Carousel Theatre), 1979 November 23-December 8; (1 of 5); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 8, Folder 62)
    - A Christmas Carol (Carousel Theatre), 1979 November 23-December 8; (2 of 5); (Photographs) (Box 8, Folder 63)
    - A Christmas Carol (Carousel Theatre), 1979 November 23-December 8; (3 of 5); (Negatives) (Box 8, Folder 64)
    - A Christmas Carol (Carousel Theatre), 1979 November 23-December 8; (4 of 5); (Production Materials) (Box 8, Folder 65)
    - A Christmas Carol (Carousel Theatre), 1979 November 23-December 8; (5 of 5); (Production Materials) (Box 8, Folder 66)
    - Three Men on a Horse (Carousel Theatre), 1980 January 25-February 9; (1 of 3); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 8, Folder 67)
    - Three Men on a Horse (Carousel Theatre), 1980 January 25-February 9; (2 of 3); (Photographs) (Box 8, Folder 68)
    - Three Men on a Horse (Carousel Theatre), 1980 January 25-February 9; (3 of 3); (Production Materials) (Box 8, Folder 69)
    - Night Must Fall (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1980 February 8-23; (1 of 4); (Programs and Press Clippings) (Box 8, Folder 70)
    - Night Must Fall (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1980 February 8-23; (2 of 4); (Photographs) (Box 8, Folder 71)
    - Night Must Fall (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1980 February 8-23; (3 of 4); (Negatives) (Box 8, Folder 72)
    - Night Must Fall (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1980 February 8-23; (4 of 4); (Production Materials) (Box 8, Folder 73)
    - The Physicists (Carousel Theatre), 1980 March 21-April 12; (1 of 4); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - The Physicists (Carousel Theatre), 1980 March 21-April 12; (2 of 4); (Photographs) (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - The Physicists (Carousel Theatre), 1980 March 21-April 12; (3 of 4); (Negatives) (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - The Physicists (Carousel Theatre), 1980 March 21-April 12; (4 of 4); (Production Materials) (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Mother Courage and Her Children (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1980 March 28-April 12; (1 of 4); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Mother Courage and Her Children (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1980 March 28-April 12; (2 of 4); (Photographs) (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Mother Courage and Her Children (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1980 March 28-April 12; (3 of 4); (Negatives) (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Mother Courage and Her Children (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1980 March 28-April 12; (4 of 4); (Production Materials) (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Arsenic and Old Lace (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1980 May 9-31; (1 of 4); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Arsenic and Old Lace (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1980 May 9-31; (2 of 4); (Photographs) (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Arsenic and Old Lace (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1980 May 9-31; (3 of 4); (Negatives) (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Arsenic and Old Lace (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1980 May 9-31; (4 of 4); (Production Materials) (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - A Mysterious Arabian Night (Carousel Children's Theatre), 1980 May 28-29; (1 of 3); (Flyer and Press Clippings) (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - A Mysterious Arabian Night (Carousel Children's Theatre), 1980 May 28-29; (2 of 3); (Photographs) (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - A Mysterious Arabian Night (Carousel Children's Theatre), 1980 May 28-29; (3 of 3); (Production Materials) (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Androcles and the Lion (Carousel Theatre), 1980 May 23-June7; (1 of 4); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Androcles and the Lion (Carousel Theatre), 1980 May 23-June7; (2 of 4); (Photographs) (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Androcles and the Lion (Carousel Theatre), 1980 May 23-June7; (3 of 4); (Negatives) (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Androcles and the Lion (Carousel Theatre), 1980 May 23-June7; (4 of 4); (Production Materials) (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Brigadoon (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1980 July 11-August 2; (1 of 4); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Brigadoon (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1980 July 11-August 2; (2 of 4); (Photographs) (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Brigadoon (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1980 July 11-August 2; (3 of 4); (Negatives) (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Brigadoon (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1980 July 11-August 2; (4 of 4); (Production Materials) (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - The Heiress (Carousel Theatre), 1980 October 31-November 22; (1 of 4); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - The Heiress (Carousel Theatre), 1980 October 31-November 22; (2 of 4); (Photographs) (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - The Heiress (Carousel Theatre), 1980 October 31-November 22; (3 of 4); (Negatives) (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - The Heiress (Carousel Theatre), 1980 October 31-November 22; (4 of 4); (Production Materials) (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Candide (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1980 November 14-29; (1 of 4); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Candide (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1980 November 14-29; (2 of 4); (Photographs) (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Candide (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1980 November 14-29; (3 of 4); (Negatives) (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Candide (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1980 November 14-29; (4 of 4); (Production Materials) (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Christmas All Over the Place, 1980 December 11; (1 of 2); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Christmas All Over the Place, 1980 December 11; (2 of 2); (Production Materials) (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - The Merchant of Venice (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1981 February 6-28; (1 of 3); (Playbills, Press Clippings, Opening Night Materials) (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - The Merchant of Venice (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1981 February 6-28; (2 of 3); (Photographs) (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - The Merchant of Venice (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1981 February 6-28; (3 of 3); (Negatives) (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - The Oldest Living Graduate (Carousel Theatre), 1981 February 20-March 7; (1 of 4); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - The Oldest Living Graduate (Carousel Theatre), 1981 February 20-March 7; (2 of 4); (Photographs) (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - The Oldest Living Graduate (Carousel Theatre), 1981 February 20-March 7; (3 of 4); (Negatives) (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - The Oldest Living Graduate (Carousel Theatre), 1981 February 20-March 7; (4 of 4); (Production Materials) (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - The Male Animal (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1981 March 27-April 18; (1 of 6); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - The Male Animal (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1981 March 27-April 18; (2 of 6); (Photographs) (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - The Male Animal (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1981 March 27-April 18; (3 of 6); (Negatives) (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - The Male Animal (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1981 March 27-April 18; (4 of 6); (Negatives) (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - The Male Animal (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1981 March 27-April 18; (5 of 6); (Production Materials) (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - The Male Animal (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1981 March 27-April 18; (6 of 6); (Financial Materials) (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Dracula: A Musical Nightmare (Carousel Theatre), 1981 April 10-15; (1 of 4); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - Dracula: A Musical Nightmare (Carousel Theatre), 1981 April 10-15; (2 of 4); (Photographs) (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - Dracula: A Musical Nightmare (Carousel Theatre), 1981 April 10-15; (3 of 4); (Negatives) (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - Dracula: A Musical Nightmare (Carousel Theatre), 1981 April 10-15; (4 of 4); (Production Materials) (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - An Italian Straw Hat (Carousel Theatre), 1981 May 15-30; (1 of 3); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - An Italian Straw Hat (Carousel Theatre), 1981 May 15-30; (2 of 3); (Photographs) (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - An Italian Straw Hat (Carousel Theatre), 1981 May 15-30; (3 of 3); (Production Materials) (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - Spelling Mistakes (Carousel Theatre), 1981 May 20-22; (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 9, Folder 54)
    - Carousel (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1981 July 10-August 1, September 25-October 3; (1 of 3); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 9, Folder 55)
    - Carousel (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1981 July 10-August 1, September 25-October 3; (2 of 3); (Photographs) (Box 9, Folder 56)
    - Carousel (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1981 July 10-August 1, September 25-October 3; (3 of 3); (Negatives) (Box 9, Folder 57)
    - Ah, Wilderness! (Carousel Theatre), 1981 November 6-21; (1 of 3); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 9, Folder 58)
    - Ah, Wilderness! (Carousel Theatre), 1981 November 6-21; (2 of 3); (Photographs) (Box 9, Folder 59)
    - Ah, Wilderness! (Carousel Theatre), 1981 November 6-21; (3 of 3); (Negatives) (Box 9, Folder 60)
    - Mr. Roosevelt's Train Never Got Here (Carousel Theatre), 1981 November 20-December 5; (Programs and Press Clippings) (Box 9, Folder 61)
    - The Confounding Christmas (UT Children's Theatre), 1981 December 9-11; (1 of 2); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 9, Folder 62)
    - The Confounding Christmas (UT Children's Theatre), 1981 December 9-11; (2 of 2); (Production Materials) (Box 9, Folder 63)
    - Medea (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1982 February 12-17; (1 of 5); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 9, Folder 64)
    - Medea (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1982 February 12-17; (2 of 5); (Photographs) (Box 9, Folder 65)
    - Medea (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1982 February 12-17; (3 of 5); (Negatives) (Box 9, Folder 66)
    - Medea (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1982 February 12-17; (4 of 5); (Production Materials) (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Medea (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1982 February 12-17; (5 of 5); (Box Office/Financial Materials) (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - For Colored Girls Who Have Considered Suicide When the Rainbow is Enuf (Carousel Theatre), 1982 February 19-March 6; (1 of 4); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - For Colored Girls Who Have Considered Suicide When the Rainbow is Enuf (Carousel Theatre), 1982 February 19-March 6; (2 of 4); (Photographs) (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - For Colored Girls Who Have Considered Suicide When the Rainbow is Enuf (Carousel Theatre), 1982 February 19-March 6; (3 of 4); (Negatives) (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - For Colored Girls Who Have Considered Suicide When the Rainbow is Enuf (Carousel Theatre), 1982 February 19-March 6; (4 of 4); (Production Materials) (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - The Two Gentleman of Verona (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1982 April 2-24; (1 of 4); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - The Two Gentleman of Verona (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1982 April 2-24; (2 of 4); (Photographs) (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - The Two Gentleman of Verona (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1982 April 2-24; (3 of 4); (Negatives) (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - The Two Gentleman of Verona (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1982 April 2-24; (4 of 4); (Production Materials) (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - The Lion Who Wouldn't (Carousel Theatre), 1982 April 20; (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Lu Ann Hampton Laverty Oberlander (Carousel Theatre), 1982 May 21-June 5; (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - The Mikado (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1982 May-July; (1 of 4); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - The Mikado (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1982 May-July; (2 of 4); (Photographs) (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - The Mikado (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1982 May-July; (3 of 4); (Negatives) (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - The Mikado (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1982 May-July; (4 of 4); (Production Materials) (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Guys and Dolls (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1982 September 24-October 16; (1 of 3); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Guys and Dolls (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1982 September 24-October 16; (2 of 3); (Photographs) (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Guys and Dolls (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1982 September 24-October 16; (3 of 3); (Negatives) (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Streamers (Carousel Theatre), 1982 October 29-November 13; (1 of 4); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Streamers (Carousel Theatre), 1982 October 29-November 13; (2 of 4); (Photographs) (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Streamers (Carousel Theatre), 1982 October 29-November 13; (3 of 4); (Negatives) (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Streamers (Carousel Theatre), 1982 October 29-November 13; (4 of 4); (Production Materials) (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - The Miser (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1982 November 19-December 4; (1 of 4); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 10, Folder 24)